<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>introduction on Gakked</title><link>/tags/introduction/</link><description>Recent content in introduction on Gakked</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 26 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/tags/introduction/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Hello World</title><link>/posts/hello-world/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/posts/hello-world/</guid><description>Starting off with one of the most over-used tropes in programming to introduce another, a tech/random thoughts/brain dump blog.
What this blog is: A place for me to write breakdowns of new topics that I encounter while working as a back-end Ruby on Rails dev An opportunity to improve my understanding of CS related topics via writing hopefully useful guides/ TIL (Today I learned) style posts A distraction from the bug tickets I am supposed to be fixing… What this blog isn&amp;rsquo;t: A comprehensive source of knowledge on any topics posted The &amp;lsquo;right&amp;rsquo; way to do things Interesting (I don&amp;rsquo;t expect anyone to read this but if one person can be helped by anything written here then that would be great) Hopefully I can share a few useful things on here and if anyone wants to get in contant please see my GH and LinkedIn linked above.</description><content>&lt;p>Starting off with one of the most over-used tropes in programming to introduce another, a tech/random thoughts/brain dump blog.&lt;/p>
&lt;h3 id="what-this-blog-is">What this blog is:&lt;/h3>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>A place for me to write breakdowns of new topics that I encounter while working as a back-end Ruby on Rails dev&lt;/li>
&lt;li>An opportunity to improve my understanding of CS related topics via writing hopefully useful guides/ TIL (Today I learned) style posts&lt;/li>
&lt;li>A distraction from the bug tickets I am supposed to be fixing…&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;h3 id="what-this-blog-isnt">What this blog isn&amp;rsquo;t:&lt;/h3>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>A comprehensive source of knowledge on any topics posted&lt;/li>
&lt;li>The &amp;lsquo;right&amp;rsquo; way to do things&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Interesting (I don&amp;rsquo;t expect anyone to read this but if one person can be helped by anything written here then that would be great)&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;p>Hopefully I can share a few useful things on here and if anyone wants to get in contant please see my GH and LinkedIn linked above.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Cheers!&lt;/p></content></item></channel></rss>